- Let's go.
- This was great.
- Man, I'm really gonna miss this.
- Me too.
- Thank you all.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you.
See you.
- What?
- Hey, see ya, punk. Bye-bye.
Yeah, me too.
Tai-chan, we need to talk to you.
- What?
- Please come to the classroom.
Just Tai-chan?
- Bye.
- I'll go back in.
- See ya.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
Me? What did I do?
Hey, so what do you think's happening?
Like, has Tai-chan done something wrong?
What's going on?
GRADUATION
FRIENDS FOR LIFE
Tai-chan,
despite many struggles and many tears,
you showed us growth.
However, until the very end,
you struggled with who to confess to,
and were uncertain about finding romance.
Mmm.
Would you like to go through
this school again,
find the woman you love,
and have another chance?
Okay.
Yeah.
BRING ON THE FIGHTS
BRING ON LOVE
BADASS #1
I've been getting into fights
since middle school.
Also shoplifting, stealing…
I used to drive around in a car I got from
a senior, and the cops would chase me.
I thought I could get away with anything.
And, I mean,
I do always get what I want, so…
I'm Ryosuke Sagae, I'm 29.
I'm from Osaka
and I have two bars in Kitashinchi.
RYOSUKE SAGAE
A.K.A. RYOPI (29)
BADASS #2
I hate being looked down on.
In our neighborhood,
if some punk rides by on their bike,
well, then that means
they're disrespecting us.
So I beat them to a pulp,
and I take their bike and helmet.
My name is Kazuma Yamaki.
I'm a tattoo apprentice,
so I work odd jobs.
KAZUMA YAMAKI
A.K.A. KAZUMA (26)
BADASS #3
Well, I've never lost a fight or a girl,
so I totally feel fine about this.
Like, bring it on.
Hey, can I beat them up?
I'm a rapper, so I can just fight them
with my words instead.
And then, well,
if they throw the first punch,
I'll beat them up,
'cause that's self-defense.
I'm Reo Kanshuji.
I'm a rapper and professional painter.
REO KANSHUJI
A.K.A. RUNE (28)
BADASS #4
I'm going to win over
the hottest girl there.
I'm the rep for a host club in Kabukicho.
I've never been rejected.
Maybe that's why people
always pick fights with me.
But I always beat them up. Yeah.
I'm Takumi Maruta.
I'm from Ishinomaki, Miyagi.
TAKUMI MARUTA
A.K.A. MARU (28)
- What're you looking at, asshole? Huh?
- Wanna go?
All right. How you doing?
- You flunked?
- Just one flunked.
He's nothing. What's this?
GRADUATION
Huh? What the hell?
- Come on, you bastard! Who are you?
- Come at me, bro.
- Bring it on, dumbass.
- Come on!
- Come at me, asshole.
- Come on.
Can't even take me like this?
Sit down.
- Will they be able to get along?
- Who knows?
Go home, Tai-chan, like, seriously.
This is too hard for Tai-chan.
- For real.
- Give him a chance.
- They're scary!
- He'll try his best.
I'm from Furukawa, Osaki,
in the Miyagi Prefecture.
I grew up surrounded by delinquents,
so I have a strong personality and look,
know what I mean?
When it's just the two of us, they get
all clingy, which is cute.
I'm Rin Horikoshi, I'm 20 years old.
I'm a hostess.
RIN HORIKOSHI
A.K.A. RINRIN (20)
I won't lose to my rivals,
I'll be very aggressive.
GOING ALL OUT, AGAINST ALL RIVALS
Hello.
Hey there.
- That all you've got?
- Welcome.
You're kidding me. So weak.
That's how she wants to start?
- She's here to fall in love, right?
- She is.
They're all there to fall in love. Yeah.
I always hated adults.
I rebelled against everything.
I'd always get into fights
at middle school.
I'd get into fights with
all the male teachers and my parents.
I have a phoenix on my back.
I just thought it was cool.
I'm Sakura. I used to work in an auto
body shop, but now I'm a nail artist.
SAKURA
A.K.A. SARA (26)
I never back down from a fight.
- Nice to meet you.
- I'm Sara.
- Hi, Sara.
- Hey.
- Where's my seat?
- Sit anywhere.
Sara, right? The only name worth knowing.
As soon as I saw her, I was like…
I thought she was amazing.
I could see that her phoenix tattoo
went the whole way down to her waist.
But below that,
I wonder what kind
of tattoo she has there.
I want to see it.
Really badly.
First of all,
my father was really abusive,
and so, at one point,
I stopped going back home
and I stopped going to school too.
In third year of middle school,
I got drunk and got into a fight.
Then I started hanging out with seniors
who were all in bike gangs.
I was taken into protective custody
almost every day.
And most of the local cops
basically became my friends.
I'm Ayana Tanaka.
I'm 24, and I work at a hostess bar.
AYANA TANAKA
A.K.A. AYACHERU (24)
- Whoa, so sparkly.
- Wow, hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, I'm Ayacheru.
- Ayacheru?
- Nice to meet you.
- It feels dangerous in here.
- Ayacheru?
I don't feel safe! I'm scared.
Sorry, excuse me.
My mom's Japanese, and my dad's Pakistani.
I got into a fight with these five guys
who were acting super-cocky
at a local hangout.
I mean, I was acting cocky too,
so I wasn't scared.
I was also engaged to somebody
who was a big-time drug dealer,
and, well, he was also a wanted criminal.
I'm Sharan Kato, I'm 21.
I work as a lounge hostess.
SHARAN KATO
A.K.A. SHARAN (21)
I haven't been with anyone
since me and my last boyfriend broke up.
So I want to kiss somebody.
Excuse me, everybody.
- Nice to meet you.
- Wow.
So intimidating.
Everyone's so intimidating.
- Nice to meet you. Looking forward to it.
- Same here.
You guys are so intimidating.
I can't remember their names.
NAGANO
- They're so scary.
- They're scary.
- Second semester students are great.
- Mmm.
- We gonna introduce ourselves then?
- Yeah, we should.
Oh, ladies first. Ladies first.
Shouldn't the guys go first?
- Fine, I'll go.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
- For real?
RYOPI (29)
OSAKA - BAR OWNER
Uh, my name is…
Ryopi the keeper. Nice to meet you.
- Ryopi.
- Nice to meet you.
So I run two bars in Kitashinchi.
- Wow.
- That's cool.
That's amazing.
What's your type?
Well, someone super fun.
Because I love comedy.
I'm your typical Kansai guy.
Oh.
- Well…
- I think that might've bombed.
Nice to meet you.
MARU (28)
TOKYO - CEO
My name is Maru. I work as a rep
for a host club in Kabukicho.
My type is a girl who is outgoing.
So I'm sort of a rapper.
Can I introduce myself
with a little rap for you guys?
Back in the day
I decked my principal in school
But now I'm reformed
No longer actin' a fool
I'm done chasin' clout
I've had enough
I'm here to fall badly in love
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice.
Yeah.
- Real nice.
- Uh…
You're writing over it?
He's writing over the messages.
Uh, I'm Kazuma.
KAZUMA (26)
KANAGAWA - PART-TIMER
Uh, I want to be a tattoo artist,
so I'm drawing pictures
while studying tattooing.
And, uh, my type is
a flashy girl with tattoos.
Nice to meet you.
- Nice.
- Okay.
Here I go.
- Whoa.
- That tattoo is incredible.
It's amazing.
SARA (26)
OKINAWA - NAIL ARTIST
My name is Sara.
I was born here in Okinawa.
I'm an Okinawan.
- Interesting.
- That's amazing.
And my type is…
Well, I like men who have
a big heart,
and who can protect me.
That's all.
RINRIN (20)
MIYAGI - HOSTESS
My nickname is Rinrin. And because
I wanna make my parents proud,
and 'cause I want to be a nail artist,
I'm working as a hostess to save money.
SHARAN (21)
FUKUSHIMA - HOSTESS
Hey, my name is Sharan.
What else do I say?
- Your profession.
- Tell us your job.
Um… Oh, yeah, I work at a lounge.
AYACHERU (24)
HOSTESS
My type of guy is
somebody fun to be around,
somebody who's easy to talk to.
That's my type of guy.
TAI-CHAN (22)
TOKYO - HAIRSTYLIST
So my name is Tai-chan.
And I'm a hairstylist.
- What a surprise.
- Uh-huh.
I thought you were a tattoo artist.
I actually just had my graduation
ceremony, but I have some regrets.
So I've decided to stay here,
at the academy,
and try my best at love again.
I hope that all of us can get along
and graduate together. Nice to meet you.
- Nice.
- Hi, Tai-chan.
Don't be sad.
- Cheer up, bro.
- Let's try our best.
So you flunked then?
Yeah.
- Sorry about before.
- Don't worry. Nice to meet you.
Can I ask why you were held back?
How did it happen?
Like, everyone gathered together here,
and it turned into this fight
over one woman between all of us.
You guys will also experience a lot
of things for the first time in here,
- but that was too difficult for me.
- Right.
- Yeah?
- That's why I decided to flunk.
- Okay.
These are the students
that will be here for the second semester.
These participants below are
who we'll be watching from now on.
I feel like the level of violence
in the atmosphere is quite high.
Yeah, you could say Kazuma
is a little quick to start a fight.
He went straight for it.
He was suddenly like "bang" and threw it.
- But he's cute when he smiles, right?
- He is cute, yeah.
- And he likes flashy girls with tattoos.
- Can you smile like that?
I haven't smiled like that
since I came to Tokyo.
Seriously.
- But Tai-chan is the most amazing 'cause…
- Right?
…even with the friendship
and family stuff,
he's probably much more
emotionally invested than we are.
Don't you think? With the others?
- From the first group?
- Yeah.
And it's been erased, just like that.
Okay, so he's going to be living
with these people from today, right?
- For two weeks, yeah.
- Isn't that tough?
- Yeah, it is.
- Uh-huh.
- Even we haven't been able to process it.
- I haven't.
I kind of thought
he wouldn't be able to process it,
but then he just said
he's gonna try his best.
Okay, let's support him.
I don't think I can root for anybody else.
You're really worrying about that?
I mean, that's how emotionally invested
we already are.
- This is totally normal.
- With the first group of students.
- Really?
- I think most viewers feel that way.
- That's right.
- I even think of the girls as enemies.
What?
1. BE ON TIME
2. NO DRUGS
3. NO THEFT
4. NO CONFESSIONS UNTIL THE FINAL DAY
5. NO INAPPROPRIATE RELATIONS ON CAMPUS
- The bell really rings.
- At this time?
I'm surprised.
You will be living together for 14 days.
You will work together
to prepare your own meals.
Today, you can drink alcohol.
- Yay!
- Oh, this is crazy!
- Fire!
- Amazing. This is it.
It's gonna get hot.
- I'll be your tour guide.
- He's guiding them.
- Tai-chan!
- Guide them.
- Here we are.
- Amazing!
- So cute!
- Oh my god. Wow!
How adorable.
- American-style.
- It's like a diner.
Yeah.
- Aren't burgers from Italy?
- America.
Shall we make something exciting?
- Or play it safe and make curry?
- Curry's good.
- Curry, then?
- Yeah.
- Let's have curry.
- You girls decided so fast.
In these situations, it's ladies choice.
I can cut vegetables, if you need me to.
- Okay.
- I'll make rice.
I can't really cook. What should I do?
I'll help with the rice.
Sure. Let's do it together.
- Ooh! Nice one, Tai-chan.
- He knows it.
- He's learned from his mistakes.
- Yeah.
- You're 22?
- Uh-huh, yeah, I'm 22.
I'm 22 in a month,
so I guess we're the same age.
- We're the same age.
- It's like I'm back in school again.
I'm looking forward to it. Mmm.
We really don't have time to waste.
- Good advice from Tai-chan the senior.
- That's his advice.
- Please, teach me.
- Sorry?
- I can't cook.
- Oh, really?
- Not at all.
- Yeah, okay.
Great. How old do you like
your guys to be?
- I like them older much older.
- Really?
- I used to date a 52-year-old.
- Fifty-two?
Crazy, right?
But it was a long time ago.
Maybe two years ago or something?
- So I was 22, and he was 52.
- Wait, that's a 30-year gap.
- Yeah.
- That's crazy.
Why did you do that?
- Well, he was a customer.
- Oh, I see.
- You fell in love with him?
- Uh-huh.
- Whoa!
- Yeah, so that happened.
Interesting.
- Finished.
- That was fast.
- So fast!
- They're perfectly peeled.
- Wait. That's Kazuma, right?
- That's Kazuma.
Chef, how do you want the cucumbers?
Shall I do them thin?
Yeah, cut them thin for the salad.
Aw, everybody here
is actually really kind.
- They are, right?
- I told you so.
You look like a craftsman.
- Right?
- I worked in a restaurant.
- You did?
- I can do all the cutting.
- That's so funny.
- But I can't cook.
- Right?
- Yeah, I know.
But I can't do carrots.
- You can't eat them?
- Right.
You're cutting them but can't eat them.
- Carrots…
- That's funny.
There we go.
Look at the colors
and flavors, it's amazing.
- Sweet and spicy, medium spicy…
- That's what it is.
- This is amazing!
- So cute.
- Stylish.
- Like a movie set.
- Oh my god. This is the best!
- This is incredible!
- What does this say?
- "Right now"?
Is it "koiyo joto"?
- It's "konsei." Well, it's not a big deal.
- No one got it right.
Okay, Class President.
Until we graduate, let's do our best.
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- That's how you do it.
- Cheers to that.
- I love this.
- This is good!
- So good.
- Oh god!
- It's so good.
- Round two.
- Wait, are you serious? That was quick.
- You okay?
- Ryopi is cute.
- He is.
- Without sunglasses.
That's right.
- So, you prefer beer?
- Beer.
- It's good, right?
- Yeah, beer's the best.
- Does anyone want my tomatoes?
- Sure, give them here. I love 'em.
- Sorry, and thanks.
- It's okay.
SARA (26)
NAIL ARTIST
RUNE (28)
RAPPER / CEO
Hey, so what's your past like?
Obviously, I got into a lot of fights.
I've had more run-ins with cops
than I can remember, but you know…
Hmm.
- My father was a very strict person.
- Hmm.
So my mom would always come pick me up
so my father wouldn't find out.
I see.
But I'll never forget
the look on my mom's face
whenever she had to do that.
At that time, I just wanted to do
the bad things 'cause it was fun.
- It was like a status symbol, right?
- Yeah. And…
I also got divorced about a year ago.
Oh, wow, okay. Uh, you're a dad?
- You have a kid?
- I'm a dad.
- What?
- What? No way!
Really? Well, that's unexpected.
But we got divorced
before the baby could really understand.
- I mean, I feel really bad for the baby.
- Hmm.
Like, I feel really guilty
that they're gonna grow up thinking
it's normal for your dad to not be around.
So how come you got divorced?
- I guess it was because I was just a kid.
- Mmm.
I was always busy with work
and I couldn't take good care of them.
Wait, how old are you?
I'm 26. I got divorced when I was 25.
Wait, what? You got divorced at 25?
- Yeah, when I was 25.
- Oh, I see.
- So, it's only been a year.
- That's what the math says.
Can I hit her?
- Hold on.
- So it's been a year.
That was funny.
- You keep following me.
- I'm not following you, I want a drink.
- They're a comedy act.
- Don't get the wrong idea.
- There's something here.
- Yeah, they look good together.
- You know, I almost got married as well.
- Mmm.
So, we'd been dating
for a year and a half,
but then he cheated on me.
- Shit.
- And he was also super abusive.
Like, he broke my phone
and took my SIM card.
- So brutal!
- That's crazy.
Yeah, he snapped it with his hands.
He also punched me really hard
in the head.
- There was so much blood.
- Seriously?
And like, I didn't know what to do,
so I just ran out of the house.
Oh.
But he caught me
and then pinned me down to beat me up.
Seriously? That's crazy!
Because I was covered in injuries,
he would've been arrested
for domestic abuse, so he locked me up.
- Until they healed?
- Mmm?
- Until they healed.
- Yeah. But, I mean, he's in jail now.
He got charged for being a drug dealer
and also for the domestic abuse.
- It's good you didn't marry him.
- Yeah.
Are you okay now?
I mean, like, emotionally.
Hmm, yeah, I'm okay.
Tai-chan hasn't said anything at all.
Yeah, Tai-chan is super quiet.
- Thanks for the meal.
- I really enjoyed that.
- Your back tattoo is amazing.
- Yeah? I guess it is.
Is it a full back? Down to your legs?
Yeah, it's a full back tattoo.
- Show me your others some time.
- Sure thing.
- We can show each other.
- I look forward to it.
Like, "What do you think
of the technique?"
Here.
- There you go. Ugh, my back hurts.
- Here.
- Oh, Rune.
- Oh, thank you.
Yeah, Rune's trying
to make a move on Sara.
You interested in anyone?
- Huh?
- Do you like anyone?
- I don't even really know anymore.
- Oh.
- Well--
- Do you?
I didn't when I first met everyone.
But I've decided to look at personalities.
Uh-huh.
You know, I'm into people
who are fun to be around.
- That's me.
- Right now, out of everyone, that's you.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I can be funny too.
Mmm-hmm? That's good.
So, I've only dated people
like that in the past.
I see, just funny guys?
- Yeah, I like people like that.
- Right.
But…
You know, my ex-boyfriend,
well, just like everyone else in here,
he was really abusive.
And, like… How do I…
He cheated on me six times
with the same girl.
Seriously?
So…
I've never really had much luck
with romance.
- Right.
- I want a healthy relationship.
So, well, my experience is,
I've been cheated on a lot in the past,
so I can get really jealous.
And because of that,
I have this strong desire
to have someone all to myself.
And so, I won't…
let them get away.
I'll catch them for sure.
- Oh, that's good.
- Amazing determination.
MEN'S BEDROOM
I guess, what I learned in the first half,
is that we don't have time
to fight among us guys.
- You tell them, Tai-chan.
- Oh, Tai-chan.
We have to go after who we like
with all we've got. Or it's over.
- Right.
- And one week will go by in a flash.
- That makes a lot of sense.
- Seriously.
I mean it. Really.
I mean, there was
only one person who flunked.
Seriously.
- Your first impressions?
- What, like when I first arrived?
I thought there were
a lot of arrogant guys.
Yeah, I get you.
- Like, that guy with a tattoo on his face?
- Oh, yeah.
So, I was like, "Damn,
that's so intimidating."
But, like, even though he has tattoos
and was acting cocky, he didn't talk.
- I know, right?
- Like when we were all eating.
But he's totally different
when it's just the two of us.
Guess that's normal.
- When it's the two of us, he talks a lot.
- Mmm.
I kind of thought he was tired
from his first romance.
I was like, "Come on,
show us you're a man."
- Right? Like, you gotta fight.
- Yeah.
He knows what happened last time,
so I wanted him to be the kind of guy
who'd be like, "Okay, let's go," you know?
- For him to take the lead.
- Yeah. Kind of pathetic, right?
Hey, don't talk shit about Tai-chan.
You literally just met him!
Tai-chan's already getting
really harshly criticized by the women.
But we already know
from having watched the first group…
- Yeah.
- …somebody will definitely like him.
- Who likes Tai-chan?
- No, you know what?
I think that they all like Tai-chan.
- Yeah, they're definitely interested.
- Okay, I see.
I mean, they're always talking
about Tai-chan.
- True.
- All of them.
If they didn't like him,
they wouldn't talk about him. I see.
I mean, if I was a girl,
I would go for Tai-chan.
- Here it is.
- What is it?
You are now going to write a love letter,
to one person here
that you're interested in.
Just one?
Yay!
- What do I do?
- Mmm…
Write an anonymous love letter
to a person that you met
who you have feelings for.
Oh, anonymous.
Please put your letters
in the mailbox outside, one by one.
WE HAVEN'T TALKED MUCH…
I'D LIKE TO TALK MORE…
- Who's Tai-chan writing to?
- Who, who, who?
SHARAN
- Okay, I see!
- Ohh!
Sharan. She has a really pretty face.
This is it.
TAI-CHAN
All right!
I put my love letter
in Tai-chan's mailbox.
We're the same age,
and he's really easy to talk to.
And he's really kind.
I'm curious about him.
Okay.
I sent my letter to Maru.
He said to me, "I don't usually cook,
so could you please teach me?"
I thought that was cute. Mmm.
I'm embarrassed.
- Oh, it's the…
- It's the keeper.
- Ryopi the keeper.
- Yeah.
He livens up the mood the most,
and it's fun talking to him.
A girl…
RINRIN
Huh, there are already couples here.
- Yeah, they look good together.
- They have the same vibe.
Kazuma's giving his to her, right?
He's given his letter to Sara,
with the tattoo.
From Okinawa.
- Who could it be?
- Oh, remember the tomatoes?
Right, yeah.
SARA
Good morning, everyone.
You will now go
to your mailbox one by one,
and check to see
if you have a love letter.
It won't be zero.
- Yeah, no way for me either.
- I feel confident about that.
What if it is zero?
- I'll jump in the sea.
- It's too early, bro.
It's raining.
That doesn't matter. It's for the feeling.
But, hey, Kazuma has
quite a pretty face, doesn't he?
Yeah. I think he's cute.
He's always smiling.
- I know!
- He's cheeky.
- He is.
- Yeah, he's really cheeky.
- So how should we announce it?
- Yeah.
Should we all show ours at once?
- At once?
- Let's do that.
But I don't want to see what's inside.
Yeah, we can hide that.
So you just do this
with your hand if you got zero.
All right.
Well, I guess I'll go first.
- Hope it goes well.
- You're getting zero.
I know I'm not getting zero.
I'm gonna come back with four.
All right.
Thanks.
- He's already back.
- Oh, he's here.
- How does he look?
- Yeah, he's grinning.
He is.
You got zero, right?
Your face says it all.
What is that?
So annoying.
- What's that mean?
- So damn annoying.
Nice
Nice.
Not zero.
Okay.
Hmm.
Damn, I thought there would be two.
- I hate how this feels.
- I know. And it's so hot.
- I want air conditioning.
- Right?
Hmm, I wonder if he has any.
Ohh!
I chose Rune.
We think the same way,
and, you know, we're both
pretty considerate of others.
So I thought we'd get along well.
Out of everyone here,
he's someone I'd really like
to get to know and talk to more.
- All right.
- Come on.
- He's going for it.
- Go for it.
No way it's zero.
Just bring the whole mailbox.
Give it a roar.
He said he'd jump
in the sea if he got zero.
He did say that.
Oh!
His face is scary again.
It's increasing.
- Well, well, well, well.
- Huh?
- Have one?
- You get one?
- Uh…
I can't tell.
- Huh?
He's fine, he's fine.
Hmm.
Should we do it on three?
- On three?
- Yeah.
Then, shall we?
- Here we go.
- Okay.
- This is bad.
- One, two, three.
- Whoa.
- Wait, we each got one?
They split them up?
- Ta-da!
- One each.
- Oh, damn it, am I the only one?
- Okay, okay, okay.
- You're the only one, huh?
- Are you serious?
I'm pissed I lost to this guy. Dang.
YOU'RE THE ONE I'M INTERESTED IN.
I'D LIKE TO TALK AGAIN.
I wonder who this is.
Her handwriting's pretty.
They're not signed.
YOU'RE THE ONE
I WANT TO GET TO KNOW THE MOST.
TO MARU, I HAD FUN MAKING CURRY WITH YOU
I'D BE HAPPY IF WE COULD TALK MORE!
THANKS FOR TODAY! WE'RE THE SAME AGE…
Is it seriously just me?
I'm damn pissed. Like, seriously?
Zero letters is tough.
I'm the only loser.
I'm surprised it was so even.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go, I'm getting super pissed.
- You're really going?
- To the sea? Yeah.
- Awesome!
- I'm a man.
- Go for it, Kazuma!
- Be careful though.
- You just watch!
- Everyone's cheering him on.
- So cute.
- It's cute.
I am a man!
Go for it, bro.
That was way too shallow.
I wanted him to jump in somewhere deep.
- Nice job.
- Awesome, bro!
That was beautiful to watch.
- It was a perfect dive.
- Yeah, super beautiful.
There was no splash at all.
I'll show you what it means to be a man!
Well said!
Leave it to me!
You think you'll get any?
- I want one from the person I wrote to.
- Yeah, I want that too.
- Of course.
- For sure, yeah.
Wow, I'm nervous.
- Hey, I'm back.
- Welcome back. How many do you have?
I got two letters.
Wait, but I haven't opened them yet.
This one is really long.
You can see through it.
"To Sharan.
I really enjoyed talking to you
so much today. Thank you."
- Oh, I've figured it out. It's Tai-chan.
- Oh, it's from Tai-chan?
"I want to get to know you
better. Let's keep on talking."
Hey, what do you think about
him having face tattoos?
- It's stylish, I like it.
- Because it's stylish? Hmm.
- Did you ask him why he got them?
- I didn't ask.
- I'm curious.
- Then who's this one from?
- Who's this from?
- I don't know!
"We have a lot in common,
so it's easy to…"
Oh, wait. I think I know.
It might be Maru.
Oh! Really?
You wrote yours to Maru, right?
- I did.
- Thought so.
Aw.
- I'm upset.
- Huh?
I didn't get a letter.
- Really?
- What?
- Yeah.
- No way!
- I feel so sad.
- Wait, who did you talk to?
- So, uh…
- Maru?
Uh, yeah, that's right.
I mostly talked to Maru.
- No way
- Then it can't be helped.
- It's just the start.
- Guess you're right.
- Yeah, stay positive.
- Right, we haven't talked to everyone.
We can make up
for it starting this morning.
- That's what a strong woman does.
- Hmm, yeah.
- She got one?
- Yeah, she does.
I'm back.
- Welcome back.
- Hey, girl.
- Huh?
- Two?
She got two! Oh, no!
No way!
- Oh, that's good.
- I can't see through it.
This one's only one line long.
- Uh, who's it from?
- Oh, I know. I know who.
- It looks like Kazuma.
- It does.
- I'm opening Kazuma's.
- Okay.
- "Sara…"
- Oh?
"We didn't get to talk much,
but I'd like to talk more."
Yeah, I think it's Kazuma.
I only talked about tattoos with Kazuma.
- That's what he means.
- Hmm.
- I'm opening it.
- Okay.
Oh, crap.
"Thanks for eating my tomatoes.
Let's drink some wine together soon."
Rune!
- Rune.
- It's Rune!
- So I've got Ryopi's?
- Yeah.
- Definitely.
- That's right.
- I'm back.
- Welcome back.
- So you got one then?
- I did.
- I knew it. It's Ryopi.
- It's kind of crazy though.
- What is?
- It had a picture.
Nice move.
"It's only the first day, but I wanna talk
more, so I'll be talking to you again."
That's so great!
- Nice! Let's see.
- I want to see the picture.
- His eyes…
- That's a great photo. So cute!
- Wait a minute.
- Look, she's already falling for him.
- Older guys are nice.
- She's already falling. She's falling.
- So cute.
- Older guys are nice.
I might get shy the next time I see him.
I want to see that.
- Your feminine side is coming out.
- Opposite to yesterday.
- I'm who they're talking about.
- It's cute.
- That's funny.
- So cute.
- Oh my god!
- That's cute.
- Oh, wow.
- Oh my god.
- She acted so hard to begin with.
- Hmm.
But when he said he liked her, she
immediately smiled, she couldn't hide it.
It makes life harder for them,
but it's also what makes them endearing.
- It's this face. She's like, "Yay!"
- Her face is so cute there.
It's scary for us, though.
When she opened the mailbox,
I was like, "What?"
I would be really scared
if she turned up outside my window.
And then, we have Sara and Rune.
Like, he passed her the napkin
so casually,
- didn't he?
- Yeah.
I think he's the type of guy who
pays attention to those little things.
That's true.
Kazuma! The girl you like
has soaking wet hands
and you just move on to the next thing.
But I guess there's also something cute
about him not noticing that.
He didn't notice, did he?
And then, Ayacheru wrote
a love letter to Maru,
but Maru ended up
writing his letter to Sharan
- So their feelings didn't line up sadly.
- Yeah.
We still don't really know how Maru feels.
Maru's a club host,
so it's hard for someone like that
to show their real feelings.
- You're right.
- I feel this is the way things will be.
- Right.
- You know? But As we start to see
everyone's characters come through,
aren't you starting to love them?
I've forgotten the first group.
- Really?
- What?
- That was fast.
- I want to focus on these guys.
- Group two?
- Yeah.
Hey, do you guys wanna eat rice?
- Want rice?
- Not that hungry?
- Then noodles? Yeah? Noodles.
- Shall we have noodles?
We'll have rice next time.
Hey, do you know where the strainer is?
- It was here.
- I can't find it.
- I haven't seen it.
- What should I do?
- Let's go for a smoke.
- Huh? Really?
- We can think while we smoke.
- We're leaving?
- For a bit.
- But everyone's confused.
- Whatever.
- That's it.
- Do all the girls smoke?
- Yeah, we do.
- Okay.
- What about the guys?
- Uh-huh, yeah, we all smoke.
- Really?
And everyone drinks too, right?
- Great, huh?
- It's amazing.
I want to know more about Okinawa.
- Hmm.
- And also about you, Sara.
Really?
But, you know,
you're everyone's type in here.
- Am I?
- You really are all the girls' type.
- Wait, am I doing something weird?
- No.
It's more that you're always smiling.
- Oh, okay.
- You're really charming.
- When did you get married?
- I got married--
- Two years ago?
- Yeah.
On August 7th…
- I, uh, lost my finger.
- Huh?
- Really? What happened?
- It was at work.
I was using a drill, you know?
- Hmm.
- I used to work on railroads.
- Railroads?
- Yeah.
- Like trains?
- Uh-huh.
Mmm.
And there were just these regular tracks,
with wooden pieces.
Uh-huh.
And we were drilling holes in the wood,
but the drill suddenly jammed.
When I tried to fix it with my hands,
my finger got caught.
- Did it hurt?
- It did.
Well, I have the same thing,
I'm actually missing a toe.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- My toe.
- Isn't it more inconvenient to lose a toe?
Not really. It's just here.
- I don't have a nail.
- Oh, yeah.
- It's just that part.
- What happened?
- Motorcycle accident.
- Oh, wow.
Yeah. But it's not inconvenient.
- It must have hurt, right?
- I don't really remember.
I was riding with my friends,
and they were like, "Where's Sara?"
They made a U-turn
and found me lying on the ground.
- Wow.
- Uh-huh, yeah it was pretty bad.
- Should we go back?
- Yeah, we've been talking too much.
We're gonna get in trouble.
- Tell me about your tattoos next time.
- Yeah, I want to.
- Yeah.
- For sure.
- Your back tattoo…
- Yeah?
I'm real curious.
I don't think anyone with a tattoo
that impressive could be a bad person.
From now on,
I'm going to pursue her so hard that
no one else will be able to make a move.
And eventually, I want to be able to have
a good look at her tattoos in the sauna.
All that's left
is boiling the soba noodles.
Okay, so in the meantime, what should--
- Wanna smoke?
- Yeah.
- It's not that bad.
- Let's go.
Yeah? What do you think?
- So you said you're a rapper, right?
- Yeah.
- Hip-hop?
I love hip-hop.
And I also love going to clubs. Yeah.
- It's nice that you like music.
- I love it.
- You know?
- Yeah.
But for real, I think it's, like,
so nice that you like music.
- I think we will get along.
- I get that, yeah.
There's different music
for different situations, right?
There's music for when you're happy,
when you're sad.
- Oh, yeah.
- You know?
- That means you can remember those times.
- I totally get that. Mmm-hmm.
For example, are there any songs
you used to love but now hate
'cause you listened to them with your ex?
- Oh my god, yeah. I can totally see it.
- Right?
You really love the song,
but it brings back memories.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
It brings back memories.
It becomes that person's song.
- It reminds you of them.
- It does. Yeah.
This is so deep. Oh my god.
- See? Yeah.
- I totally get it.
He was, like, so deep.
He really thought about things. I guess
it's because he's a rapper, you know?
And when I asked him
why he became a rapper…
What did he say?
I've forgotten.
I forgot what he said,
but it was something real deep.
It can't have been that deep
or she wouldn't have forgotten.
So, yeah, I'm really curious
to find out more about him.
Mmm.
- Let's eat.
- Thanks for cooking.
- Thanks, everyone.
- Let's eat.
Is it good?
Speaking as someone from Okinawa?
- Yeah, it's really delicious.
- Oh, yeah?
It's really good.
It's relaxing.
What's coming?
It's the evening sauna time.
- Here it is!
- First time.
Our first sauna.
The person who goes
is one of the ones
who received the most love letters,
Sara or Sharan.
- Really?
- Nice one, guys.
- Which one?
- I've just eaten. No!
- You will decide with a game of darts.
- Oh, this is amazing.
The winner will get to choose
the man she wants to sauna with.
- Here we go.
- Can you play?
- Amazing.
- I'll give it a go.
So whoever gets nearest the center wins.
That's the easiest way to do it.
- So just one throw?
- Just one throw.
- One throw.
- Let's do this.
Let's go.
- One throw.
- Sounds good.
- Nearest the bullseye wins?
- Yeah.
- The sauna at night is nice.
- Yeah?
- Oh, it's night.
- Beautiful.
- I want to go.
- Let's see how this goes.
Let me try.
Here I go.
- Go, go, go!
- Yeah.
You've got this!
Do it! Do it!
Kazuma really wants
to see Sara's tattoos in the sauna.
- Exactly.
- Here I go.
- Go for it.
- Will I hit it?
Whoa!
- That's close.
- Nearly got it!
- I wanna go into the sauna.
- It's gonna be close.
- Any last words, pretty lady?
- Was it here?
- One more step forward.
- Any last words?
I'll do my best.
- Oh my god!
- Ooh, ooh!
- You two are amazing.
- Good match.
- It was a really good match.
- The winner is Sara!
- Congratulations.
- Nice.
Congrats.
- I wanted to go.
- That was impressive.
So, the person I would like
to invite to the sauna is…
Oh? Drumroll please…
Uh…
Boom.
- Rune.
- All right!
Look at that. The first sauna.
Can we go now?
- That was quick.
- Super quick.
- I wanna go.
- Should I set it up, or…
- See you later.
- We're going.
The first sauna.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
REFRESHED
- Hey there.
- Hi.
- Isn't this amazing?
- It looks really good.
I'm nervous.
Oh my god. This is the real deal.
- Look.
- Oh, this is amazing.
- Right?
- Better than I imagined.
- This is a loyly, right?
- Yeah.
Oh my god. Hilarious.
If I'm honest,
I was torn between you and Kazuma.
- Oh, about who to invite?
- Yeah.
Kazuma was also saying that
he wanted to come in here with me.
- Mmm-hmm.
- He was
telling me how he's super curious
about my tattoos.
So I was torn between who to choose.
But you're the one
who I wrote my letter to,
and so, I decided that I wanted
to come in here with you.
- Wow, I'm so happy.
- Really?
Thank you.
- So I wrote my love letter to you.
- Yeah.
I only wrote three lines.
I hope that was okay?
- Yeah, totally fine.
- I couldn't think of anything to write.
I was like, "What should I do?
I talked to him but…
what should I write?" That was
the first love letter I've ever written.
- Oh, it was?
- I've only written to people in prison.
Oh my god.
They drop it in so casually.
I've never used the word "prison"
in casual conversation.
Letters are important
for people in prison.
I've only written to friends
who were in prison.
So this was the first time since then--
No, it was the first time in my life.
- That makes me happy.
- Does it?
- How come you started rapping?
- Rapping?
Well, the thing is,
I always wanted to be a real hero.
What? What do you mean? Like a superhero?
Yeah, exactly.
I always wanted to be a hero.
Right.
I entered the Junon Superboy Contest,
thinking it would make me a hero.
- Really?
- I was accepted.
Wow.
And I was chosen
as the 25th Junon Superboy.
Mmm.
And about a year and a half later,
I became a Kamen Rider.
What? A Kamen Rider? What do you mean?
- A Kamen Rider.
- Wearing the suit?
Not the guy inside the suit.
I was in the Kamen Rider show
for about a year.
- You became a Kamen Rider?
- Yeah.
- And--
- That's crazy!
- Yeah.
- Oh my god. That's so funny!
Yeah. So, I got a lot of other acting jobs
off of the back of that.
But I had always wanted to be
a Kamen Rider,
so I felt like I had accomplished my goal,
- and I was burned out.
- You felt satisfied? I see.
- I felt like I was missing something.
- The opposite?
- There was a hole in my heart.
- Oh.
Yeah. And rap was
what filled that hole for me.
- Oh, that's amazing.
- Yeah.
- It's interesting.
It's starting to piss me off.
So, do you, like,
wanna be a famous rapper?
That's my number one goal. With rapping.
What, so you wanna go global?
Mmm, yeah, I want to go global, but…
- So a little while ago, my…
- Mmm.
…my mother got cancer.
- For real?
- Yeah.
- No way.
So…
- Way back then,
- Hmm.
I would go into the studio,
like, all the time,
- Hmm.
- 'cause I was always making songs.
- I didn't spend much time with my family.
- Mmm, yeah.
And so, then I… I guess I realized,
that I should spend more time
with my family.
Hmm.
So if I live my life the proper way,
I can see them when I wake up
in the morning.
And I can have dinner with them
when I come home.
And then I can just do
my own thing during the day.
And when I had my first live performance,
it was at a really small venue,
but she was still able to come.
- For real?
- Yeah.
And it was my first time performing.
I didn't have any fans, and I didn't even
tell my friends about it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It really was like
I was performing on my own.
- Anyway, she was the only one who came.
- Oh god.
And while everyone
was just sitting there in silence…
I mean, it's okay, nobody knew my name,
and my songs
weren't exactly good back then, so…
Hmm.
But I gave it my all.
And she was the only one
who was like,
"You're so cool! You're the best!"
- Really? That's so sweet.
- She was the only one cheering me on.
- So touching.
- And it made me so, so happy, you know?
Oh my god. I feel so moved. It's too much.
- Yeah.
- That's so sweet.
- And so, that's why…
- Hmm.
…I wanna make it big.
Hmm.
So she can see me perform
at a big venue sooner rather than later.
Oh my god. That's so sweet.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
That's my biggest goal.
Of course, I want to go global too.
Yeah, I get that. Of course.
I'm getting really pissed off.
- Okinawa has loads of rappers.
- Yeah.
Like, so many.
But it is still really hard
to get into the industry.
I don't often get
to go this deep with people.
- I'm so moved.
- Glad to hear it.
- Don't do it!
- No, Kazuma, please don't. Jeez!
Other people have been through
a lot of the same stuff.
- No.
- It's Jason from Friday the 13th!
Seriously. He's like Jason.
Kazuma!
- Huh?
- Oh my god. What? Jason?
- I'm sorry.
- Is this a horror show?
No.
Is this the one where he's alive?
- No.
- I know what to do.
Give him an electric shock.
No, really. Tell me, do women actually
fall for this kind of thing?
- I wouldn't say I don't like it.
- Well…
I do feel bad for Kazuma,
but Rune is way cooler,
in terms of looks and the way he lives.
That's how it is.